Preliminary Inventory of the Committee on the Present Danger records
Hoover Institution Archives
- CQ Weekly and conferences (Folder 313)
- Soviet politics and leadership, 1979-1985 (Folder 314)
- Soviet politics and leadership, 1986- (Folder 315)
- Soviet economy, 1978- (Folder 316)
- Soviet nuclear forces, 1976-1984 (Folder 316)
- Soviet nuclear systems, 1985- (Folder 317)
- Soviet politics press clippings (Folder 318)
- Soviet economy press clippings, 1990-1992 (Folder 319)
- Middle East, 1981 (Folder 320)
- Air Force documents on environmental impact analysis process (Folder 320)
- Air Force documents on environmental impact analysis process (Folder 321)
- Middle East, 1978-1979 (Folder 321)
- Middle East, 1981 (Folder 322)
- Middle East, 1980 (Folder 323)
- Middle East, 1980 (Folder 324)
- Middle East, 1980 (Folder 325)
- Middle East, 1980 (Folder 326)
- Photographs (10 envelopes), circa 1979-1982 (Folder 327)
- Jewish Institute for National Security Affairs (JINSA) materials and newsletters, 1980-1982 (Folder 327)
- American Committe on East-West Accord materials and newsletters, 1978-present (Folder 327)
- Arms Control Today newsletters (Folder 327)
- Executive Committee meeting, 18 Sep 1981 (Folder 327)
- Executive Committee meeting, 24 Jun 1981 (Folder 327)
- Executive Board Meeting, 13 Mar 1981 (Folder 327)
- Executive Committee meeting, 8 Feb 1980 (Folder 328)
- Executive Committee meeting, 27 Mar 1980 (Folder 328)
- Executive Committee meeting, 27 Jun 1980 (Folder 328)
- Executive Committee meeting, News Clips, 12 Oct 1979 (Folder 328)
- Executive Committee meeting, 17 Dec 1979 (Folder 328)
- Preferred Press Conference Work Sheets 7 Jun 1905 (Folder 328)
- Loose material from Neswire (Folder 328)
- Teller press conference, National Press Club, 1 Oct 1986 (Folder 328)
- "Where We Stand on Arms Control" Press Conference, 16 Jul 1986 (Folder 328)
- Jefferson Hotel Press Conference, 17 Oct 1985 (Folder 328)
- The Economics of Defense (Stein) Press Conference, 8 Mar 1985 (Folder 329)
- Jefferson Hotel Press Conference, 24 Oct 1985 (Folder 329)
- Jefferson Hotel Press Conference, 19 Apr 1984 (Folder 329)
- Press Conference Jefferson Hotel, 26 Apr 1984 (Folder 329)
- "Can America Catch Up?" press conference, Jefferson Hotel, 30 Nov 1984 (Folder 329)
- Washington press and syndication list, 1983-1984 (Folder 329)
- Press Conference, 29 Jun 1982 (Folder 329)
- Has America Become Number 2 requests (Folder 329)
- Washington press and syndication list, 1982 (Folder 329)
- Reagan Defense program press conference, 17 Mar 1982 (Folder 329)
- Press conference, 9 May 1980 (Folder 329)
- Press conference, 1980 (Folder 330)
- CRISIS Cosmos 23 Jan 1980 (Folder 330)
- Clips for annual meeting, 1 Nov 1990 (Folder 330)
- Press Conferences, 17, 24 Oct 1985 (Folder 330)
- Alerting America Press Coverage (Folder 330)
- "Can America Catch Up?" Press Reaction (Folder 330)
- "Can America Catch Up?" Press Conference, 30 Nov. 1984 (Folder 330)
- Defense & the Deficit Press Reaction (Folder 330)
- CPD press clippings (Folder 331)
- Press Conference, 19 April 1984 and 26 April 1984 (Folder 331)
- Nitze App-CPD mention and other mentions (Folder 331)
- C-SPAN transcripts and comments (Folder 331)
- Press clippings, 1984 (Folder 331)
- Clippings for next Board meeting, 1983 (Folder 331)
- press clippings distributed at Executive committee meetings (6 folders), February 1982 to November 1983 (Folder 332)
- CPD meetings, 1984-1989 (Folder 333)
- Reagan campaign (Folder 333)
- Present Danger, Regional, international groups and regional meetings (Folder 333)
- Present Danger, rival groups, East-West, New Directions (Folder 333)
- Executive Committee meetings and correspondence, 1990 (Folder 333)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 12 Mar 1992 (Folder 333)
- Executive Committee Meeting about dissolution of CPD, 1 Nov 1991 (Folder 333)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 9 Jan 1990 (Folder 333)
- List of Board of Directors, 1989, 1990 (Folder 333)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 17 Mar 1989 (Folder 333)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 28 Jan 1988 (Folder 333)
- CPD Executive Committee minutes, Feb 1976-22 May 1987 (Folder 334)
- Executive Committee agenda, notices, and correspondence, 1987 (Folder 334)
- Executive Committee agenda, notices, and correspondence, 1986 (Folder 334)
- Executive Committee agenda, notices, and correspondence, 1985 (Folder 334)
- Executive Committee agenda, notices, and correspondence, 1983 (Folder 335)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 22 May 1987 (Folder 335)
- Richard Allen's warning to journalists so they would not tarnish his reputation anymore "vindication" (Folder 335)
- Executive Committee agenda, notices, and correspondence, 1982 (Folder 335)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 18 Mar 1983 (Folder 335)
- Executive Committee agenda and notices, 1981 (Folder 336)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 7 Dec 1982 (Folder 336)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 21 Jan 1982 (Folder 336)
- Memos to Board, 1982 (Folder 337)
- Memos to Board, 1976-1981 (Folder 337)
- Richard Allen, Executive Committee, 1979-1984 (Folder 337)
- Miscellany (Folder 338)
- Contributors recapitulations, 1982-1987 (Folder 338)
- Contributors list, 1986 (Folder 338)
- Solicitations (Folder 338)
- Magazines (Folder 339)
- Strategic Defense Initiative, 1983-1984 (Folder 340)
- Strategic Defense Initiative, 1989 (Folder 340)
- Strategic Defense Initiative, 1987 (Folder 341)
- Strategic Defense Initiative, 1988 (Folder 342)
- Strategic Defense Initiative, 1985 (Folder 342)
- Strategic Defense Initiative, 1986 (Folder 343)
- Space / Strategic Defense Initiative (Folder 344)
- BMD-Strategic Defense Initiative, 1985 (Folder 344)
- Magazines (Folder 345)
- Magazines (Folder 346)
- Soviet non-compliance, 1986 (Folder 346)
- Non-compliance issues (Folder 347)
- Soviet non-compliance, 1985 (Folder 347)
- Soviet non-compliance, 1987 (Folder 347)
- HSRC (Folder 348)
- Soviet non-compliance, 1984 (Folder 348)
- Soviet non-compliance, 1979-1983 (Folder 348)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Balance, 1983-1984 (Folder 349)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Balance, 1985- (Folder 349)
- 1981 Reagan Str. Mod. Program (Folder 350)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Balance, 1980-1982 (Folder 350)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Balance, 1976-1979 (Folder 351)
- "Can America Catch Up?" copies (Folder 352)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Balance-Is America Still Number 2? materials, including a letter of comment by Richard Stilwell, under-secretary of Defense, and Richard Perle, both thinking the report is too pessimistic. (Folder 353)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Balance-Is America Still Number 2? material, mainly draft annotated copies, and a letter from Charls Walker to Charles Tyroler, 2 July 1984 (Folder 354)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Balance-Is America Still Number 2? material draft annotated copies and proofs (Folder 355)
- Hearings, Iran-Contra affair (Folder 355)
- The Price of Being Number 2 draft and a paper by W. Van Cleave (Folder 355)
- More of the same (Folder 356)
- More of the same; loose material; letter form D Trachtenberg to Tyroler (Folder 357)
- Air Force documents on environmental impact analysis process (Folder 358)
- Middle East, 1981 (Folder 359)
- Middle East, 1983 (Folder 359)
- Middle East, 1983 (Folder 360)
- Briefing Service organization Sulgrave, January 1979 (Folder 360)
- Middle East, 1981 (Folder 360)
- Middle East, 1982 (Folder 361)
- Middle East, 1982 (Folder 362)
- Middle East, 1981 (Folder 363)
- Hugh Scott correspondence (Folder 364)
- Herbert Stein-Walker Project (Folder 364)
- Charles Tyroler, II (Folder 364)
- John P. Roche, correspondence, 1976-1991. Materials range from the letter from Rostow asking for his participation (9/15/76) to his resignation (Folder 365)
- Eugene V. Rostow correspondence and articles, 1988-1991 (Folder 365)
- Eugene V. Rostow 1988-1989. Includes a draft letter to the board suggesting dissolution, date 2 Apr 1992 (Folder 365)
- Nitze materials and correspondence, including resignation from CPD, 5 October 1990 (Folder 366)
- Prof. Richard E. Pipes (Folder 366)
- October 1985 Poll Jefferson Hotel, 17, 24 October 1985 (Folder 367)
- U.S. Public Attitudes Toward the Nuclear Freeze and Other Nuclear Arms Issues, 19 Apr 1984 (Folder 367)
- "Can America Catch Up?", Press Conference, 30 Nov 1984 (Folder 367)
- U.S. Public Attitudes Towards the Defense Effort-Program, Priorities and Budget, 26 Apr 1984 (Folder 367)
- Charles Burton Marshall (Folder 367)
- The Economics of Defense (Stein) (Folder 368)
- "Where We Stand on Arms Control" Press Conference, Jefferson Hotel, 16 Jul 1986 (Folder 368)
- U.S. Public Attitudes on Arms Control, National Press Club, 20 Aug 1986 (Folder 368)
- Public Attitudes Toward the U.S. Defense Effort, National Press Club, 27 Aug 1986 (Folder 368)
- Teller pres conference, National Press Club, 1 Oct 1986 (Folder 368)
- National Security Affairs conference, 2 Oct 1986 (Folder 368)
- National Press Club, 15 Apr 1987 (Folder 368)
- National Press Club Press Conference, 20 Apr 1987 (Folder 368)
- U.S. Senators from Muskie to Humphrey, 1978-1980. See also boxes 88-89 (Folder 369)
- Working group papers and notes (Folder 370)
- U.S. Senators from Inouye to Bayh, 1978-1980. See also boxes 88-89 and 369 (Folder 371)
- Meetings with Media Editorial Boards (Folder 371)
- Present Danger, Warnke (Folder 371)
- Current News, articles, hearings (Folder 371)
- SALT Senate (Folder 372)
- Loose materials (Folder 373)
- Videocassette (Folder 373)
- U.S. Senators from Jepsen to Leahy, 1978-1980See also boxes 88-89 and 369 (Folder 373)
- Press Conference, 24 Nov 1987 (Folder 374)
- Press Conference, 30 Nov 1987 (Folder 374)
- New National Poll on U.S. Nuclear Weapons, 26 May 1988 (Folder 374)
- Detailed Analysis of Soviet Defense Spending, 16 May 1989 (Folder 374)
- Is America Catching Up? The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance,1989 (Folder 374)
- Senator Henry Jackson (D) Washington (2 folders) (Folder 374)
- Eastern Europe, 1981 (Folder 375)
- Caribbean and Latin America materials, 1984- (Folder 375)
- Middle East, Dec-90 (Folder 376)
- Caribbean and Latin America materials, 1983 (Folder 376)
- Caribbean and Latin America materials 1983 (Folder 377)
- Caribbean and Latin America materials, 1982 (Folder 377)
- Central and Latin America materials, 1977-1982 (Folder 378)
- Eastern Europe, 1982 (Folder 379)
- Eastern Europe, 1983 - (Folder 379)
- Articles and By-laws (Folder 380)
- Lists, including Board members in government service (Folder 380)
- Board members, expired terms (Folder 380)
- Eastern Europe, 1982 (Folder 380)
- Foundation Proposal: A Grand Strategy for the Free World Foundaton Proposal, Military Balance (Folder 381)
- A Proposal: The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance (Folder 381)
- CPD Annual Reports to D.C. Legal (Folder 381)
- French,, John-Apll. for Grant (Folder 381)
- CPD Legal: Non-Profit Ruling DC US (Folder 381)
- Loose material on the same subject (Folder 381)
- Renzy, Bernard T., Special Counsel (Folder 381)
- CPD Legal DC Tax exemption (Folder 381)
- Trademark Application Renewal 1988 (Folder 381)
- Loose material-correspondence with Smith Richardson Foundation, early 1980's (Folder 382)
- CPD Foundations: Noble (Folder 382)
- CPD Foundations: Scaife (Folder 382)
- CPD Foundations: Miscellaneous (Folder 382)
- Contribution Lists, 1987-1992 (Folder 383)
- Van Cleave, William R. (Folder 384)
- Fund Raising: Corporate Nos.,1986- (Folder 384)
- Contribution Lists, 1986 (Folder 384)
- Acheson, David C. (Folder 385)
- Adelman, Kenneth L. (Folder 385)
- Allen, Richard V., Executive Committee, 1987-1989 (Folder 385)
- Allen, Richard V., Executive Committee, 1985-1986 (Folder 386)
- Earle, Valerie A. (Folder 386)
- Graham, William (Folder 386)
- Kupperman, Charles M. (Folder 386)
- Mallory, C. King III (Folder 386)
- Loose books and reviews (Folder 387)
- U.S.-Soviet Relations, 1977-1983 (Folder 388)
- Reagan Summits, 1981-1985 (Folder 389)
- U.S.-Soviet Relations, Pres. Gorbachev, 15 June 1985. See Succession file (Folder 390)
- U.S.-Soviet Relations, Nov 1982-14 January 1985 Andropov / Chernenkosee Succession file (Folder 391)
- U.S.-Soviet Relations, Brezhnev, Oct 1980-Nov 1982 (Folder 391)
- ABM (US). Contains material from Heritage on High Frontier Project (Folder 392)
- Loose material on Western-Soviet relations (Folder 393)
- Loose material, including books on NATO, defense budget and various subjects (Folder 394)
- Soviet Defense Spending/ technology, 1976-1984 (Folder 395)
- Soviet Space Activity (Folder 395)
- Soviet ABM / Air Defense (Folder 396)
- Soviet Defense Spending Technology, 1985- (Folder 396)
- Soviet Convent / General Military (Folder 397)
- Soviet Conventional forces, 1983-1987 (Folder 398)
- KAL-007 (Folder 398)
- KAL-007 (Folder 399)
- Soviet Conventional forces, 1988- (Folder 399)
- Current News loose issue (Folder 400)
- Current News loose issue (Folder 401)
- Congressional Record on Defense Budget (Folder 401)
- EX-TET File. Contains material on plans to combine a strong defense and a balanced budget and reduce the deficit (Folder 402)
- Defense budget and charts, FY 1984 (Folder 402)
- Budget Graphs, FY 1985 (Folder 402)
- Budget Analysis, FY 1984/ FY1985 (Folder 402)
- DoD Budget, FY 1985 (Folder 402)
- Budget Analysis (Folder 402)
- DoD Budget, FY 1984 (Folder 403)
- DoD Budget-Congress, FY 1985 (Folder 403)
- DoD Budget, FY 1983 (January-June 1982) (Folder 404)
- DoD Budget, 1983 (Folder 405)
- Budget, FY 1984 (Folder 405)
- DoD Budget, Senate Debate, FY 1982 (Folder 406)
- DoD Budget, FY 1982 (Jan.-June 1981) (Folder 406)
- Budget, FY 1990 (Folder 407)
- Defense Budget (Folder 407)
- DoD Budget, FY 1982 (July-Dec. 1981) (Folder 407)
- Budget, FY 1980 (Folder 408)
- Nuclear Carrier (Folder 408)
- U.S. Defense Contractors (Folder 408)
- RDT and E through FY 1982 (Folder 408)
- U.S. Defense Budget, 1979 (Folder 408)
- U.S. Army Programs (Folder 409)
- U.S. Navy Programs (Folder 409)
- U.S. Navy Programs, 1979 (Folder 409)
- U.S. Air Force Programs (Folder 410)
- CX (Folder 410)
- Tankers (Folder 410)
- A-10 (Folder 410)
- F-18 (Folder 410)
- Current News Loose issues (Folder 411)
- Budget Congress. Debate, FY 1983 (Folder 411)
- Defense Budget Loose material. Contains material on China (Folder 412)
- START, 1982 (Folder 413)
- START, 1983 (Folder 413)
- START, 1984 (Folder 414)
- Theater Nuclear Weapons Talks (Folder 414)
- INF, 1982 (Folder 414)
- SALT (Reagan) (Folder 414)
- TNF (Reagan) (Folder 415)
- Arms reduction talks loose material (Folder 415)
- Arms reduction talks loose material (Folder 416)
- MBFR / CSBM / CFE, 1990- (Folder 417)
- MBFR / CSBM / CFE, 1989 (Folder 417)
- INF, 1984 (Folder 417)
- Asia and the Pacific 1978-1979 (Folder 418)
- Afhganistan, 1981- (Folder 418)
- Asia and the Pacific, 1981-1982 (Folder 419)
- Asia and the Pacific, 1980 (Folder 419)
- Asia and the Pacific, 1983- (Folder 420)
- Afghanistan, January, 1980 (Folder 421)
- Eastern Europe, 1979-1980 (Folder 422)
- Afghanistan, 1978-1979 (Folder 422)
- SALT II, loose material including a ring-binder from Senate Foreign Relations Committee, "SALT Handbook and SALT II Treaty Book," June 22, 1979 (Folder 423)
- Afghanistan, 1980 (Folder 423)
- defense and foreign affairs loose material (Folder 424)
- Loose material (Folder 425)
- Mallory, CK MA thesis (Folder 425)
- Das Committee on the Present Danger"-eine case study zur Mobilisierung von Öffentlichkeit in der amerikanischen Politik," Schriftliche Hausarbeit zur Erlangung des Grades eines Magister Artium (M.A.) der Philosophischen Fakultät des Christian-Albrechts-Un1986 (Folder 425)
- Loose material, including correspondence by Rostow (Folder 426)
- Financial material, including petty cash receipts, check books, etc. (Folder 427)
- Loose material, including CPD seal machine, bank receipts (Folder 428)
- Middle East, April-May 1991 (Folder 428)
- Middle East, March 1991 (Folder 429)
- Bank receipts (Folder 429)
- Strategic Review Loose issues (Folder 460)
- MBFR / CFE Chronology (Folder 430)
- Middle-East, June-December 1991 (Folder 431)
- Middle-East, Feb. 1991 (Folder 432)
- Gulf War (Folder 432)
- Middle-East, Jan-91 (Folder 433)
- Gulf crisis loose Material (Folder 434)
- 1980 Campaign-General (Folder 435)
- Reagan: Defense and Foreign Policy (Folder 435)
- Reagan campaign (Folder 436)
- 1980 Campaign-General (Folder 436)
- 1980 Campaign Editorials / articles (Folder 436)
- 1980 Campaign: Cartoons, Graphics, etc. (Folder 436)
- Bank receipts (Folder 437)
- Bank receipts (Folder 438)
- Bank receipts (Folder 439)
- Invoices; parking (Folder 440)
- CPD: KCR Copy Service, 1977-1984 (Folder 440)
- Catterton Printing, etc. (Folder 441)
- Press Intelligence, 1986-1991 (Folder 441)
- CPD/ Pro-Typists, Inc. (Folder 441)
- nuclear weapons and Navy Loose articles on (Folder 442)
- military subjects various Loose material on (Folder 443)
- Financial records (checks, etc.), 1985 (Folder 444)
- Financial records, including contributions 1982, 1981-1984 (Folder 445)
- Financial records, including contributions, 1976-1981 (Folder 446)
- Article in Commentary, Richard Pipe, "Why the Soviet Union Thinks It Could Fight and Win a Nuclear War" (Folder 447)
- Meeting 18 Feb 1977 (Folder 447)
- Committee on the Present Danger Meeting, 15 Dec 1976 (Folder 447)
- Press Conference, Committee on the Present Danger, 11 Nov. 1976. Contains transcript of the press conference (Folder 447)
- National Press Club Press Conference Committee on the Present Danger, 11 Nov. 1976 (Folder 447)
- Committee on the Present Danger, 1977. "Public/Congressional Relations Plan for the CPD" prepared by Alan Woods (Folder 447)
- Rostow Group Augmentation. 4, Luncheon, 1976 (Folder 447)
- CPD Chronology, 1978 (Folder 447)
- Newspaper Articles (Folder 447)
- Rostow Group 2 file (Folder 447)
- Rostow Group paper "A Time for Change" (Folder 447)
- Rostow Group # 1 file (Folder 447)
- CPD-Houston Solicitation, Sept. 1977 (Folder 447)
- Contributor Mailings in chronological order (Folder 447)
- The Nations Editors... brochure (Folder 447)
- Loose articles (Folder 448)
- Hearings on the Iran-Contra affair (Folder 448)
- Hearings on the Iran-Contra affair (Folder 449)
- Articles, generally on the Iran-Contra affair, 1986-1987 (Folder 450)
- U.S.-Soviet Military Facts-CDI (Folder 451)
- Center for Security Policy (Folder 451)
- Closeup Foundation, Other Organizations (Folder 452)
- Committee for National Security, and material by Paul Warnke and Ann Cahn (Director) (Folder 452)
- Committee for Nuclear Responsibility (Folder 452)
- Committee ON U.S. Interests in Middle East (Folder 452)
- Common Ground (Folder 452)
- Conservative Caucus (Folder 452)
- Conservative Network (Folder 452)
- Council for a Liveable World (Folder 452)
- CSIS Panels (Folder 452)
- Material on the CDI (Folder 453)
- Defense Monitor loose issues (Folder 453)
- Defense Monitor (Folder 453)
- Democrats for Defense (Folder 453)
- Families for Defense (FFD) (Folder 453)
- Ground Zero (Folder 453)
- Heritage foundation publications (Folder 454)
- High Frontier newsletter (Folder 454)
- Hoover Institution (Folder 454)
- Institute for Policy Studies (Folder 454)
- Intelligence Digest (Folder 454)
- International Security Council (Folder 455)
- Lawyers Alliance for Nuclear Arms Control (Folder 455)
- Media Monitor (Folder 455)
- Nuclear War "Projects" (Folder 455)
- Peace-PAC (Folder 455)
- Physicians for Social Responsibility (Folder 455)
- RAND Corporation (Folder 455)
- SIPRI (Folder 455)
- Union of Concerned Scientists (Folder 455)
- WILPF (Folder 455)
- Iran-Contra affair articles and op-eds (Folder 456)
- Iran-Contra affair articles and op-eds (Folder 457)
- Iran-Contra affair loose material (Folder 458)
- Iran-Contra affair loose material (Folder 459)
- Loose material (Folder 459)
- Russian Military Expenditures, 24 Apr 1991 (Folder 460)
- Carter Administration: Jimmy Carter (Folder 460)
- Carter Administration (Folder 460)
- Carter Administration (Folder 461)
- Carter, Billy,"Billygate" (Folder 461)
- Administration Arms Control Statements (Folder 461)
- Editorials (Folder 461)
- Republican National Convention, Detroit, 1980 (Folder 461)
- Presidential Primaries, 1980 (Folder 462)
- Republican Platform, 1980 (Folder 462)
- Senators' Statements (Folder 462)
- Senate Elections, 1980 (Folder 462)
- Congress-Campaign, 1980 (Folder 462)
- Debate: Iowa, 1980 (Folder 462)
- Iowa Caucuses, 1980 (Folder 462)
- Transition (articles only) (Folder 462)
- Contribution Lists, 1976-1981 (Folder 463)
- Fowler Letters, 1979 (Folder 463)
- Fundraising, 1985 (Folder 463)
- Fundraising Letters, 1978-1984 (Folder 463)
- Contributions Declined, 1979-1982 (Folder 463)
- Fundraising Finance Committee, Fundraising projects (Folder 463)
- Financial Supporters, 1977 (Folder 464)
- Committee on the Present Danger: Fundraising Pre-Announcement (Folder 464)
- Fundraising: Corporate Nos (Folder 464)
- Contribution Lists (Folder 464)
- Contributors Lists (Folder 464)
- Contributors check copies (Folder 464)
- Contribution Lists, 1982-1985 (Folder 464)
- Campaign, 1984 (Folder 465)
- Primaries, 1984 (Folder 466)
- Primaries, 1984 (Folder 467)
- Financial records (Folder 468)
- Financial records (Folder 469)
- Iran-Contra affair hearings (Folder 470)
- Ronald Reagan, 1980 (Folder 471)
- Ronald Reagan, 1980 (Folder 472)
- Strategic Command, Control, Communications (C I) (Folder 472)
- Strategic Forces (Folder 472)
- Strategic Nuclear Forces (SNF) (Folder 472)
- NATO (Folder 472)
- Theater Nuclear Force (TNF) (Folder 472)
- Defense Budget, FY 1981 (Folder 473)
- Defense Budget, FY 1981 (Feb.-May 1980) (Folder 473)
- Defense Budget, FY 1981 (June-Dec. 1980) (Folder 473)
- Press clippings on CPD (Press Intelligence, Inc.), 1979 to 1982 (Folder 474)
- Press clippings on CPD (Press Intelligence, Inc.), 1980 (Folder 475)
- Press clippings, 1977-1978. Including articles in the Soviet press and in VFW (Folder 476)
- Press clippings, 1978 (Folder 476)
- Press clippings on CPD (Press Intelligence, Inc.), 1979 (Folder 476)
- Present Danger: Press Notices, 1976-1978. Containing press clips on CPD (Folder 477)
- Press clips on CPD, 1978 (Folder 478)
- Citizens Committe for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam materials (Folder 479)
- Material from CPD (Folder 479)
- Citizens Committe for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam materials (Folder 480-488)
- Is the Reagan Administration's Defense Program Sufficient For Countering the Soviet Threat? CPD Pamphlet. Contains material and drafts for this pamphlet, which had also been entitled "Countering the Soviet Threat-U.S. Defense Strategy in the 1980s," and will be finally titled "Is the Reagan Defense Program Adequate" (see also box 169 and others) (Folder 489)
- "Has America Become Number Two?-The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance and American Defense Policies and Programs" material and press clippings (Folder 489)
- "Has America Become Number Two? The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance and American Defense Policies and Programs" material and press clippings. Also contains material on the same pamphlet, including comments by R.W. Komer, Valerie Earle, Charles Burton Marshall, David Trachtenberg. Pamphlet was to be called "Will America Remain Number Two? Propping Open the Window of Vulnerability" (Folder 490)
- Balance Sheet Legislative File. Contains material on the same pamphlet, comments and draft annotated copies (Folder 491)
- "Quick Fixes to U.S. Strategic Nuclear Forces," April 1980. Contains material on the draft for the CPD Quick Fix pamphlet (Folder 491)
- "Has America Become Number Two?-The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance and American Defense Policies and Programs," draft annotated copies (Folder 492)
- Balance Sheet U.S.-Soviet Military Balance, 1980Contains original draft by WVC, May 1980, orignally titled "America Is Becoming Number Two: The Growing Military Imbalance" (Folder 492)
- "Has America Become Number Two?-The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance and American Defense Policies and Programs" material (Folder 493)